Guide to the Records of Graham Windham 1804-2011 MS 2916
New-York Historical Society
- Series III - Graham Windham, 1970-2011 (bulk 1977-2010)
  - Subseries III.9 - Office of Development - Photographic Materials, circa 1978-2010
    - Makeup Demonstration FOGW - prints, 1985 (Offsite-box 89, Folder 4)
    - Graham School Miscellaneous - prints, negatives, 1984, 1986 and undated (Offsite-box 89, Folder 5)
    - Family Day Care - prints, negatives, contact sheets, circa 1970-1987 (Offsite-box 89, Folder 6)
    - Family Day Care Fire Safety Workshop - prints, negatives, slides, 1984 (Offsite-box 89, Folder 7)
    - Mental Health Center - prints, contact sheets, 1984 (Offsite-box 89, Folder 8)
    - Day Care Center - prints, negatives, 1982 (Offsite-box 89, Folder 9)
    - Foster Care - Mrs. Lockhart and Family - prints, contact sheets, 1987 (Offsite-box 89, Folder 10)
    - Slides, circa 1984 (Offsite-box 89, Folder 11)
    - Grow With Us - prints, negatives, 1985 (Offsite-box 90, Folder 1)
    - Grow With Us - prints, negatives, slides, 1985 (Offsite-box 90, Folder 2)
    - Grow With Us - prints, negatives, 1985 (Offsite-box 90, Folder 3)
    - Grow With Us and Babies Prep- prints, correspondence, 1985 (Offsite-box 90, Folder 4)
    - Kids Miscellaneous - prints, negatives, contact sheets, 1979 and undated (Offsite-box 90, Folder 5)
    - Volunteers - prints, negatives, undated (Offsite-box 90, Folder 6)
    - Junior Committee - slides, prints, contact sheets, 1984 and undated (Offsite-box 90, Folder 7)
    - Doris Duke Fund/Clinic - prints, negatives, undated (Offsite-box 90, Folder 8)
    - Junior League Halloween Party - prints, undated (Offsite-box 90, Folder 9)
    - Junior League Cookie Exchange - prints, circa 2004 (Offsite-box 90, Folder 10)
    - Annual Meeting - prints, slides, negatives, 1984-1985 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 1)
    - Annual Meeting - prints, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 2)
    - Corporate Run - contact sheets, negatives, 1992 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 3)
    - MLK Jr. School Dedication with Al Roker - prints, negatives, contact sheets, 1992 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 4)
    - 52nd Street Project - prints, negatives, 1992 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 5)
    - Japanese Exchange Student Tour - prints, negatives, contact sheets, 1992 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 6)
    - Residential Treatment Center Community Luncheon - prints, negatives, contact sheets, 1992 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 7)
    - Christmas Tree Lighting - Rockefeller Center - prints, negatives, 1993 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 8)
    - Residential Treatment Center - Firemen and Christmas Presents - prints, negatives, contact sheets, 1993 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 9)
    - Japanese Exchange Event - prints, contact sheets, 1993 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 10)
    - Social Workers Luncheon - contact sheets, negatives, 1993 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 11)
    - Santa/Hastings-on-Hudson Fire Dept. Visit to Campus - prints, 1994 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 12)
    - Rwanda Relief! - prints, 1994 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 13)
    - Christmas Party - prints, negatives, 1995 and 1997 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 14)
    - Christmas Party and Other Parties - prints, 1985-1987 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 15)
    - B. Smith Party - prints, negatives, contact sheets, 1989 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 16)
    - B. Smith Party - prints, negatives, contact sheets, 1990 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 17)
    - Harbor Bank Event - prints, contact sheets, 1990 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 18)
    - JWP Christmas Party, David Dinkins and Melba Moore - prints, negatives, 1990 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 19)
    - Event - Joyce Lapenn, President - contact sheet, negative, 1991 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 20)
    - Ministers Breakfast including Calvin Butts - prints, contact sheets, 1988-1989 (Offsite-box 91, Folder 21)
    - Congressman Jose Serrano Event - prints, undated (Offsite-box 91, Folder 22)
    - Miscellaneous Photos - prints, circa 1985-1989 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 1)
    - Group Homes - negatives, 1 print, 1980-1984 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 2)
    - Clarendon Group Home Dinner Speaker - print, undated (Offsite-box 92, Folder 3)
    - Group Homes - prints, contact sheets, circa 1978-1987 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 4)
    - Snyder Group Home - Joyce Lapenn Visit, undated (Offsite-box 92, Folder 5)
    - Group Homes Christmas Party - print, 1988 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 6)
    - Group Homes Christmas Party - prints, 1989 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 7)
    - Group Homes Channel 13 - prints, 1989 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 8)
    - Group Homes Rockaway Garden - mounted prints, 1989 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 9)
    - Group Homes- prints, contact sheets, 1990 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 10)
    - Group Homes Children to San Juan - prints, contact sheets, 1990 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 11)
    - Malcolm X Group Home - prints, negatives, contact sheets, 1990 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 12)
    - Grow with Us - prints, contact sheet, 1990 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 13)
    - Grow with Us - prints, negatives, 1990 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 14)
    - Residential Treatment Center Zone 13 Performance 52nd St Project - prints, negatives, contact sheets, 1990 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 15)
    - Group Homes Brooklyn Office - contact sheet, 1991 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 16)
    - Group Homes Children at L.I.U. - prints, negatives, contact sheets, 1991 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 17)
    - Neighborhood Family Service Center - print, contact sheet, 1991 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 18)
    - Neighborhood Family Services Picnic - prints, 1991 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 19)
    - Crown Heights Consortium Meeting - prints, negative, 1992 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 20)
    - Grow with Us New York Cares Day - prints, negatives, contact sheets, 1992 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 21)
    - Malcolm X Bulb-a-Thon - prints, negatives, contact sheet, 1992 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 22)
    - Neighborhood Family Service Center - contact sheets, 1992 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 23)
    - Parkside Group Home Girls - prints, negatives, 1992 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 24)
    - Brooklyn Neighborhood Center - prints, contact sheet, 1993 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 25)
    - Group Homes Volleyball Clinic - prints, negatives, contact sheets, 1993 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 26)
    - Grow With Us - prints, contact sheets, 1993 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 27)
    - Square Dance - prints, negatives, contact sheets, 1993 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 28)
    - Harlem Day Care Center Opening - prints, 1994 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 29)
    - Youth Council Meeting - contact sheet, 1994 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 30)
    - Fall/Winter Newsletter Photos - prints, 1989 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 31)
    - Spring Newsletter Photos - prints, 1990 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 32)
    - Fall/Winter Newsletter Photos - prints, 1990 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 33)
    - Spring/Summer Newsletter Photos - prints, 1991 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 34)
    - Fall/Winter Newsletter Photos - prints, 1991 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 35)
    - Spring/Summer Newsletter Photos - prints, 1992 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 36)
    - Fall/Winter Newsletter Photos - prints, contact sheet, 1992-1993 (Offsite-box 92, Folder 37)
    - Adoption Fair, 1985-1991 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 1)
    - Brooklyn Day Care Children, undated (Offsite-box 93, Folder 2)
    - Old Brooklyn Day Care, 1986 and undated (Offsite-box 93, Folder 3)
    - Brooklyn Day Care General, 1989 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 4)
    - Brooklyn Day Care Christmas, 1990 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 5)
    - Brooklyn Day Care/Dalton Children, 1991 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 6)
    - CWLA Conference/Catherine Tracy, 1986 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 7)
    - Family Day Care General, 1989 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 8)
    - Finest Care Dedication, 1989 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 9)
    - Finest Care Staff and Children, 1989 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 10)
    - Finest Care Playground, 1991 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 11)
    - Finest Care Children and Staff, 1992 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 12)
    - Finest Care Graduation, circa 1993 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 13)
    - Finest Care Easter Egg Hunt, 1993 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 14)
    - FOGW Music Project, undated (Offsite-box 93, Folder 15)
    - W.F. FOGW Planting Day, 1988 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 16)
    - Foster Boarding Home with Muppets, undated (Offsite-box 93, Folder 17)
    - Foster Boarding Home Toys for Tots, 1986 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 18)
    - Foster Boarding Home - NatWest Bears Xmas, 1989 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 19)
    - Foster Boarding Home Christmas Party, 1990 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 20)
    - Foster Boarding Home Christmas Party, 1991 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 21)
    - Foster Boarding Home Christmas Party, 1992 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 22)
    - Foster Boarding Home Opening Present, 1992 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 23)
    - Foster Boarding Home Miscellaneous, 1992 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 24)
    - Sweatshirt Party FOGW, 1985 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 25)
    - Grow with Us, undated (Offsite-box 93, Folder 26)
    - Residential Treatment Center Alumni Reunion (1960-1980), 1988 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 27)
    - Residential Treatment Center Chess Story, 1989 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 28)
    - Residential Treatment Center Fall Planting, 1989 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 29)
    - Residential Treatment Center Tree Lighting, 1989 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 30)
    - Residential Treatment Center Wynton Marsalis Visits, 1989 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 31)
    - Residential Treatment Center Alumni Day, 1990 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 32)
    - Residential Treatment Center Tree Lighting, 1990 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 33)
    - Residential Treatment Center Annual Tennis Awards, 1990 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 34)
    - Residential Treatment Center Tennis Tournament, 1990 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 35)
    - Denver Developmental Training, 1993 (Offsite-box 93, Folder 36)
    - Miscellaneous Photos including Music Center Dedication, 1997-1998 and undated (Offsite-box 93, Folder 37)
    - Manhattan Mental Health Center Opening, 1989 (Offsite-box 94, Folder 1)
    - Manhattan Mental Health Center Lipton's 10 Tons of Food, 1990 (Offsite-box 94, Folder 2)
    - Welcome Home Thanksgiving and Christmas, 1990 (Offsite-box 94, Folder 3)
    - First Lady of Burkina Faso Visit, 1991 (Offsite-box 94, Folder 4)
    - St. John's Day Care Center, 1991 (Offsite-box 94, Folder 5)
    - Manhattan Center General, 1991 (Offsite-box 94, Folder 6)
    - Welcome Home, 1991 (Offsite-box 94, Folder 7)
    - Welcome Home P.A.T. Open House, 1991 (Offsite-box 94, Folder 8)
    - Fake TFBH Photos for Newsletter, 1992 (Offsite-box 94, Folder 9)
    - FLB at Parkside, 1992 (Offsite-box 94, Folder 10)
    - Lewis Children Lemonade Stand 33IP, 1992 (Offsite-box 94, Folder 11)
    - PAT Graduation, 1992 (Offsite-box 94, Folder 12)
    - Manhattan Center Softball Team, 1993 (Offsite-box 94, Folder 13)
    - Manhattan Center Young Sisterhood Collective, 1993 (Offsite-box 94, Folder 14)
    - Rockefeller Flower Show Project, 1993 (Offsite-box 94, Folder 15)
    - Project Welcome Home Baskets, 1993 (Offsite-box 94, Folder 16)
    - Campus Planting Day, 1988 (Offsite-box 94, Folder 17)
    - May Taylor Day on Campus and other Campus Photos, 1996 (Offsite-box 94, Folder 18)
    - Campus Luncheon, 2001 (Offsite-box 94, Folder 19)
    - Campus, Joyce Lapenn, Poul Jensen, Charmaine Wong, Susan Gunn, undated (Offsite-box 94, Folder 20)
    - Campus Barbecue, undated (Offsite-box 94, Folder 21)
    - Campus (Greenburgh Graham School), 1995-1996 (Offsite-box 94, Folder 22)
    - Campus (Greenburgh Graham School), 1998 (Offsite-box 94, Folder 23)
    - Holiday Party FOGW, 1987 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 1)
    - Staff Photos, 1989-1991 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 2)
    - Staff Recognition Dinner, 1989 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 3)
    - Staff Picnic, 1990 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 4)
    - Staff Recognition Dinner, 1990 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 5)
    - Dorothy Rumph (Staff), 1990 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 6)
    - Graduation - Pre-Service Training, 1992 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 7)
    - Staff Picnic, 1992 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 8)
    - Staff Recognition Lunch, 1992 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 9)
    - Team Building Exercise, 1992 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 10)
    - Annual Staff Meeting, 1993 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 11)
    - Irving Place Staff, 1993 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 12)
    - Irving Place Medical Clinic, 1993 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 13)
    - Nurses Week, 1993 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 14)
    - NY Friends Ornament Party, 1988 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 15)
    - NY Friends Makeup Party, 1989 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 16)
    - NY Friends Ornament Party, 1989 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 17)
    - NY Friends Miscellaneous, 1989 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 18)
    - NY Friends T-shirt Party, 1989 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 19)
    - NY Friends Thanksgiving Turkey, 1989 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 20)
    - NY Friends Makeup Party, 1990 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 21)
    - NY Friends T-Shirt Party, 1990 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 22)
    - Volunteers United Way Award, 1989 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 23)
    - Westchester Friends Spring Planting, 1989 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 24)
    - Volunteers - Toys, 1990 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 25)
    - In-Service Graduation, 1991 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 26)
    - Volunteer Training at Irving Place, 1991 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 27)
    - Bronxville Friends Story Hour, 1992 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 28)
    - Brooklyn Junior League Quilting Project, 1992 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 29)
    - Group Homes Makeup Party, 1992 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 30)
    - Volunteer Recognition Luncheon, 1992 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 31)
    - Westchester/Fairfield Friends Arts Committee, 1992 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 32)
    - Manhattan Center Tea for Bronxville Friends, 1993 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 33)
    - Volunteer Recognition Luncheon, 1993 (Offsite-box 95, Folder 34)
    - Westchester Friends, undated (Offsite-box 95, Folder 35)
    - Spring Gala (Jim Henson), 1986 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 1)
    - Henson Journal, 1986 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 2)
    - Gala, 1986-1988 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 3)
    - Spring Gala (Diane Sawyer), 1988 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 4)
    - Arthur Ashe Benefit Journal, 1987 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 5)
    - Residential Treatment Center Arthur Ashe Visit, 1989 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 6)
    - Japanese Group at Gates Avenue, 1989 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 7)
    - Spring Gala (Arthur Ashe, Winton Marsalis), 1989-1990 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 8)
    - Spring Gala (Oscar de la Renta), 1991 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 9)
    - Spring Gala (Maurice Sendak), 1992 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 10)
    - Spring Gala, 1993 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 11)
    - Steel Band at Pan Am Building, undated (Offsite-box 96, Folder 12)
    - Regina Darby Christmas Party, 1987 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 13)
    - Minister's Breakfast, 1989 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 14)
    - New York Friends Benefit, 1989 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 15)
    - Manufacturers Hanover Run, 1990 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 16)
    - Marsalis Family Concert, 1990 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 17)
    - Minister's Breakfast, 1990 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 18)
    - Residential Treatment Center Garden Club, 1990 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 19)
    - Benefits Fair, 1991 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 20)
    - Great Expectations, 1991 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 21)
    - MHT Corporate Run, 1991 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 22)
    - Minister's Breakfast, 1991 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 23)
    - Residential Treatment Center Cottage Dedication, 1991 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 24)
    - Residential Treatment Center Spring Planting Day, 1991 (Offsite-box 96, Folder 25)
    - Board Members, 1990 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 1)
    - President Joyce Lapenn, undated (Offsite-box 97, Folder 2)
    - Poul Jensen and Joyce Lapenn, 1997 and undated (Offsite-box 97, Folder 3)
    - Holidays and Projects at ? including with Poul Jensen, undated (Offsite-box 97, Folder 4)
    - Les Edwards, 1997 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 5)
    - The Rev. Dr. Calvin O. Butts 3rd, undated (Offsite-box 97, Folder 6)
    - Portrait of Isabella Graham by J.W. Jarvis - Original at Campus, undated (Offsite-box 97, Folder 7)
    - Residential Treatment Center - contact sheet, circa 1989 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 8)
    - Residential Treatment Center - contact sheet, circa 1989 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 9)
    - 1990s Activities Various Locations, 1994-1997 and undated (Offsite-box 97, Folder 10)
    - Contact Sheet and Photos - Activities - Various Locations, 1990 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 11)
    - Baseball Park, 1999 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 12)
    - The Beacon Center, circa 1990-1999 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 13)
    - Campus Various Activities, 1990 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 14)
    - Activities at Campus, 1994-1996 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 14)
    - Campus Buildings Renovated, circa 1990-1999 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 15)
    - Late 1990s Campus, circa 1995-1999 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 16)
    - Ground Breaking Residential Treatment Center, 1990 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 17)
    - Volunteer Award Winners, circa 1990-1999 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 18)
    - Cottage Dedication Residential Treatment Center - contact sheet, 1991 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 19)
    - Beacon Opening, 1993 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 20)
    - Family Day Care, 1993 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 21)
    - Harlem Child Care Center Opening, 1993 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 22)
    - Three People in Front of Family Court, 1994 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 23)
    - Rwanda Car Wash Benefit, 1994 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 24)
    - Alumni and Staff at Campus, 1996 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 25)
    - Annual Meeting, 1997 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 26)
    - Foster Parent Recognition, 1997 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 27)
    - Contact sheet location?, 1997 (Offsite-box 97, Folder 28)
    - Christmas Celebration, undated (Offsite-box 97, Folder 29)
    - Bronxville Friends, Family of New York with Matilda Cuomo, undated (Offsite-box 97, Folder 30)
    - Ainslie Cottage Dedication, 1994 (Offsite-box 98, Folder 1)
    - Alvin Ailey Dance School, 1994 (Offsite-box 98, Folder 2)
    - Essence Magazine and Johnson and Johnson Fantasy Story Hour, 1994 (Offsite-box 98, Folder 3)
    - Holiday Party at Campus, 1994 (Offsite-box 98, Folder 4)
    - Julie Saker and Joel Dubenity - E. Hamilton Scholars on Campus, 1994 (Offsite-box 98, Folder 5)
    - May Taylor Day at Campus, 1994 (Offsite-box 98, Folder 6)
    - Harlem Day Care Center, 1994 (Offsite-box 98, Folder 7)
    - 1994-95 Annual Meeting (Offsite-box 98, Folder 8)
    - Consumers Union Volunteer Painting Odell Cottage, 1995 (Offsite-box 98, Folder 9)
    - Children at Campus, 1995 (Offsite-box 98, Folder 10)
    - Holiday Celebrations/Campus and Family Child Care, 1995 (Offsite-box 98, Folder 11)
    - Post Legal Adoption Meeting, 1995 (Offsite-box 98, Folder 12)
    - Harlem Child Care Center also Picture of Judith Jemison, 1995-1996 (Offsite-box 98, Folder 13)
    - Foster Parents Recognition Day Contact Sheet, 1996 (Offsite-box 98, Folder 14)
    - Harlem Child Care Center Contact Sheet Various Activities, 1996 (Offsite-box 98, Folder 15)
    - Independent Living, 1996 (Offsite-box 98, Folder 16)
    - Williamsburg Center Halloween, 1996 (Offsite-box 98, Folder 17)
    - Bronxville Community Service, 1997 (Offsite-box 98, Folder 18)
    - Harlem Child Care Center Graduation, 1997 (Offsite-box 98, Folder 19)
    - Remington Boys and Girls Club, 1997 (Offsite-box 98, Folder 20)
    - Volunteer Recognition Luncheon, 1997 (Offsite-box 98, Folder 21)
    - Viacom Cleanup Harlem Day Care Center, 1997 (Offsite-box 98, Folder 22)
    - U.S. Trust Company Contact Sheet - Tour by Children, 1998 (Offsite-box 98, Folder 23)
    - Activities at Campus, 1999-2000 (Offsite-box 98, Folder 24)
    - Campus Buildings - Basements, 2000 (Offsite-box 98, Folder 25)
    - Westchester Volunteers, 2000 (Offsite-box 98, Folder 26)
    - Various Activities Harlem Day Care Center, 2001 (Offsite-box 98, Folder 27)
    - Harlem Child Care/Hewitt School Volunteers, 2003 (Offsite-box 98, Folder 28)
    - Grow With Us - Hewitt School Volunteers, 2003 (Offsite-box 98, Folder 29)
    - Campus Basketball Benefit, 2003 (Offsite-box 98, Folder 30)
    - Graham School Trip on the Sloop Clearwater, 2004 (Offsite-box 98, Folder 31)
    - Harlem Child Care - Ogilvy and Mather Volunteers, 2000-2004 (Offsite-box 98, Folder 32)
    - Finest Day Care Center - Graduation?, 2000-2004 (Offsite-box 98, Folder 33)
    - 33 Irving Place Staff, 1993 (Offsite-box 99, Folder 1)
    - Phyllis Barr, Archivist, 1993 (Offsite-box 99, Folder 2)
    - Staff, Dr. Cynthia Boakye, Attending Pediatrician, 1992 October (Offsite-box 99, Folder 3)
    - Alexandra Bowie, Director, Quality Assurance, 1993 (Offsite-box 99, Folder 4)
    - Staff, Dr. Jennie Brown, Director Residential Treatment Center, 1991 (Offsite-box 99, Folder 5)
    - Paul Dunn, Director, Family Community Support Division, 1991 (Offsite-box 99, Folder 6)
    - Staff, Fatima Goldman, Director, Early Childhood Education, 1991 (Offsite-box 99, Folder 7)
    - Finest Staff, Monika Graff, undated (Offsite-box 99, Folder 8)
    - William Hamer III, V.P., Community Program Services, 1991 (Offsite-box 99, Folder 9)
    - Staff, Sylvia Isabel, Adoption Recruitment Coordinator, 1991 (Offsite-box 99, Folder 10)
    - Staff Gloria Jones-Grant, Director of Manhattan Mental Health Center, 1990 May (Offsite-box 99, Folder 11)
    - Staff, Joyce Lapenn, President, 1988 (Offsite-box 99, Folder 12)
    - Staff, Joyce Lapenn, President, and Fatima Goldman, Dir. of Early Childhood Education, 1990 May (Offsite-box 99, Folder 13)
    - Joyce Lapenn, Executive Director, President, 1991 (Offsite-box 99, Folder 14)
    - Carmine Magazino, 1986 (Offsite-box 99, Folder 15)
    - Staff, Dr. Evelyn Opoku, Director Health Services, 1991 December (Offsite-box 99, Folder 16)
    - Staff, Barbara G. Patterson, Director of Nursing, 1992 October (Offsite-box 99, Folder 17)
    - Staff, Richard Primason, Director of Therapeutic Services, 1992 September (Offsite-box 99, Folder 18)
    - Staff, Albert J. Rodriguez, Director Residential Treatment Center, 1993 (Offsite-box 99, Folder 19)
    - Anita Sorensen, Director FBH and Adoption Div., 1991 (Offsite-box 99, Folder 20)
    - Family Day Care - MAPP Training Session, 1992 (Offsite-box 99, Folder 21)
    - Halloween Party, Staff, 1991 (Offsite-box 99, Folder 22)
    - Foster Boarding Homes, 1995 (Offsite-box 99, Folder 23)
    - Volunteers and Misc., 1998 (Offsite-box 99, Folder 24)
    - Gala, 1998 (Offsite-box 99, Folder 25)
    - Gala, 1998 (Offsite-box 100, Folder 1)
    - Gala, 1998 and 2001 (Offsite-box 100, Folder 2)
    - Gala, 2000 (Offsite-box 100, Folder 3)
    - Gala, 2001 (Offsite-box 100, Folder 4)
    - Gala, circa 2001-2002 (Offsite-box 100, Folder 5)
    - Gala, 2004 (Offsite-box 100, Folder 6)
    - Board members incl. Michael Golden, Staff Member Frank Spain, CFO Chair Georgia Wall, and author Tom Wolfe, circa 2000-2005 (Offsite-box 100, Folder 7)
    - Chelsea Piers Gala incl. Michael Golden, Georgia Wall, and Tom Wolfe, circa 2000-2005 (Offsite-box 100, Folder 8)
    - Gala with photos of Chair Michael Golden and author Tom Wolfe, circa 2000-2005 (Offsite-box 100, Folder 9)
    - Gala with French Ambassador Jean-David Levitte, 2007 (Offsite-box 100, Folder 10)
    - Mockup for Greenburgh-Graham Brochure, circa 1984 (Offsite-box 101, Folder 1)
    - Five Year Report Photographs, circa 1984-1986 (Offsite-box 101, Folder 2)
    - Pictures of Children/Annual Report, circa 1978-1989 (Offsite-box 101, Folder 3)
    - Annual Report Photos, 1989 (Offsite-box 101, Folder 4)
    - Annual Meeting, 1990 (Offsite-box 101, Folder 5)
    - Annual Report Photos incl. Ted Koppel, 1990 (Offsite-box 101, Folder 6)
    - Suzanne Bales and Michael Ainslie at Gala, 1990 (Offsite-box 101, Folder 7)
    - Annual Report Photos, 1991 (Offsite-box 101, Folder 8)
    - Sandra Trim DaCosta, Board Member, 1991 (Offsite-box 101, Folder 9)
    - Johnson and Higgins Donation, 1991 (Offsite-box 101, Folder 10)
    - Banco de Popular Donation, 1991 (Offsite-box 101, Folder 11)